https://www.sigmanu.org/about-us/general-information/privacy-policy

About Us - General Information - Privacy Policy - Sigma Nu Fraternity, Inc.
DonateMember Login/Register
Search:
Menu
About UsGeneral InformationCopyright NoticeTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyVision, Mission, and Strategic PlanThe Creed of Sigma Nu FraternityHistoryState of the Fraternity & FoundationVisiting HeadquartersFraternity LeadershipStaff DirectoryEmploymentMerchandiseOfficial Insignia & ArtworkInterfraternal InvolvementFifth Point Properties, LLCExpansionExpansion FAQExpansion ResourcesCurrent & Future ColoniesRecently Charted ChaptersIs Your Chapter Dormant?Chapter ListingActive Chapters & ColoniesDormant ChaptersMedia ReleasesCollegiate MembersPandemic PlanPast StatementsUpdated Pursuit of Excellence ProgramUpdated Chapter Consultation ProgramMental HealthBest Practices LibraryVirtual OperationsService and PhilathropyCampus LeadershipValues Congruent EnvironmentsIntellectual DevelopmentCandidate DevelopmentBrother DevelopmentAlumni DevelopmentRecruitment and ManpowerChapter OperationsGovernance and AccountabilityUsage and HistoryOfficer ResourcesCommanderLt. CommanderTreasurerRecorderRisk Reduction ChairmanScholarship ChairmanSocial ChairmanMarshalLEAD ChairmanHouse ManagerCommunity Service & Philanthropy ChairmanChaplainAlumni Relations ChairmanRecruitment ChairmanEducational ProgramsV-A-RAnti-Hazing InitiativeNational Hazing Prevention WeekHazingPrevention.OrgGreekLifeEduAlcoholEduBehind Happy FacesMental Health Quick TakesDignityUPoster SeriesStrengths WorkshopsGenerationRxDon't Play DoctorMentor NetworkAdvisorsAdviseesFAQScholarsHelping Hand InitiativePartnersMonth of ServiceCrowdChangeLEAD ProgramPhasesAll ChapterPhase IPhase IIPhase IIIPhase IVEvaluationFAQGet Started With LEADLeadership ResourcesSession EvaluationTeam BuildingLead ChairmanVolunteeringPursuit of ExcellenceIn-Person OperationsValues-Based LeadershipPersonal Development & Membership ValueOperational ExcellenceVirtual OperationsValues-Based LeadershipPersonal Development & Membership ValueOperational ExcellenceChapter Support ProgramValues-Based RecruitmentEducational MaterialsMarketing MaterialsMultimedia MaterialsRecruitment ResourcesChapter Consultation & SupportLeadership Consultation ProgramLeadership ConsultantsSchedulesBecome a ConsultantRisk ReductionChapter ResourcesWe Have A SituationRisk Reduction ChairmanSocial ChairmanSocial PlanningSpecial Event Request FormIncident Report FormEventsGrand ChapterCollege of ChaptersSigma Nu InstitutesCollegiate & Chapter AwardsLEAD Program AwardsPursuit of Excellence AwardsRock Chapter AwardsAlumni & VolunteersPandemic PlanHouse Corporation ResourcesAlumni Volunteer ResourcesMental HealthBecoming a VolunteerAlumni Advisory BoardsGuidelinesMentoring and AdvisingOfficer UpdateAssessment ProgramChapter AdvisorsRole of Chapter AdvisorsAlumni Best Practices LibraryAlumni Advisory BoardsHouse CorporationsAlumni DevelopmentAlumni EngagementUsage and HistoryMental Health ResourcesMentor NetworkAdvisorsAdviseesFAQHigh CouncilDivision CommandersRiley SocietyAlumni ChaptersPetitionGovernanceOperationsAnnual ReportListingSurveyAlumni ClubsGuidelinesListingRegister Your Alumni ClubEventsGrand ChapterSigma Nu Institutes150th Anniversary ReceptionsLocal EventsAlumni Awards & DistinctionsHall of HonorHall of Fame150th DirectoryChange of AddressProspective MembersGeneral InformationWhy Sigma NuLeadershipServiceAcademicsNo HazingLEAD ProgramValueHistoryThe FoundersHonorThe CreedVision and MissionProspective Member FormAre You a Legacy?Legacy Information for AlumniMembership ReferralActive Chapter & Colony ListingNotable Sigma Nu MembersScholarshipsInformation for ParentsLEADParticipantsPhase IPhase IIPhase IIIPhase IVEducational FoundationAbout the FoundationVision and MissionStrategic PlanBoard of DirectorsBrandon S. AversBen A. BuettellThomas J. BymarkCharles R. EitelTodd E. EliasonJohn A. HearnTimothy C. HuffmyerRobert J. LalanneDaniel W. MaslauskiJames R. MounierMaxwell L. SmithJonathan D. SprengerAlbert W. WursterStaffBrad BeachamDavid M. MainellaNicholas L. MurphyShannon T. BalserKenneth W. LewisVolunteer OpportunitiesCollegiate Board MemberYoung Alumnus Board MemberPrioritiesEmergency Scholarship FundInformation for Applicants150th Anniversary BrickSpears Family Epsilon Epsilon Center for ExcellenceDonation FormCollege of ChaptersNational Scholarship FundsFounders General Scholarship FundChapter Scholarship AccountsBeta Tau Chapter Scholarship AccountEpsilon Omicron Chapter Scholarship AccountEta Zeta Chapter Scholarship AccountTheta Kappa Chapter Scholarship AccountTheta Sigma Chapter Scholarship AccountKappa Lambda Chapter Scholarship AccountLambda Upsilon Chapter Scholarship AccountMu Zeta Chapter Scholarship AccountMichael Patrick Joyce (Mu Xi) Scholarship FundChapter Educational FundsBeta Zeta Chapter Educational FundBeta Theta Chapter Educational FundGamma Beta Chapter Educational FundLambda Epsilon Chapter Educational FundHeadquarters PropertyMemorial Flag Pavilion & War MemorialWays to GiveDonate NowUpdate Payment InformationAdvice 4 CommandersPlanned GivingThanks & Recognition1869 Club1869 Club Chapter Challenge1869 Club Donation PagePathway of HonorBrick Order FormMemorial Flag PavilionBrick Order FormWar MemorialDonor ListingCumulative GivingOmega SocietyYates Legacy SocietyEventsAtlanta Honorary BoardBlack & Gold SocietyWhy join the Black and Gold Society?What are the benefits and levels of the Black and Gold Society?How can I serve as a Black and Gold Society ambassador?Why do alumni support the Black and Gold Society?Black & Gold Society AmbassadorsAmbassador Sign-UpThe DeltaLatest NewsCurrent IssuePast IssuesBlog
About Us
Privacy Policy
Sigma Nu Fraternity, Inc.Sigma Nu Educational Foundation, Inc.Fifth Point Properties, LLC
Sigma Nu Fraternity, Inc. and Sigma Nu Educational Foundation, Inc. take your privacy very seriously. We want you to understand what information we may gather, how we protect it, and how we may use it. Please read the following to learn and understand more about our privacy policy.
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how Sigma Nu treats personal information that it collects and receives. Personal information is information that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies or other entities that Sigma Nu does not own or control or to people that Sigma Nu does not employ or manage. This website may contain links to other websites. If you link to another website, this policy will not apply to your use of said website, or the data collection practices of said website.
Information Collection
Sigma Nu Fraternity, Inc. and Sigma Nu Educational Foundation, Inc. are the owners of the information collected on this website. We collect information from our users at several different points on our website.
General
The website uses a variety of methods to collect and use information from our users. This information is collected through the use of online forms (registration forms, merchandise order forms, surveys, etc.) cookies, log files, third-party advertising, and clear GIFs. For an explanation of these information collection tools and how they are used, please see the section on Information Use.
Registration for Members
In order to use the Members Area, a member must first complete the registration form. In order for the registration to begin, the user must provide unique personally identifiable information. During the registration, a user is required to agree to the Terms of Agreement and give contact information (such as name, address and e-mail address). It is optional for the user to provide demographic information and some other personal information. The user will also have the ability to opt in or out of services provided either through the website or other Sigma Nu related activities. In some instances, such as Initiation Registration within the Members Area, personal financial information will be collected (such as credit card number, expiration date).
Registration for New Candidate Members
In order to gain access and register as a New Candidate, the user must complete the registration form and select a payment option. During the registration, a user is required to agree to the Application for Membership and the Terms of Agreement and give contact information (such as name, address, phone numbers and e-mail address). It is optional for the user to provide demographic information and some other personal information. The user will also have the ability to opt in or out of services provided either through the website or other Sigma Nu related activities. Additionally the New Candidate will have to select a payment option for the payment of the Candidate Fee, this information may include personal financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).
Donations, Event Registrations, and Merchandise Orders
We request information from the user on our order forms, donation forms, and registration forms. A user must provide certain contact information (such as name, e-mail, and addresses) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer orders or requests. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user. The information may also be used to acknowledge donations, orders, or registrations for events.
Various Forms and Surveys
The website contains various forms through which information is collected for a variety of purposes. This information is collected for its stated purpose and used in accordance to the stated policies within this Privacy Policy.
Information Use
We use information collected from the website in a variety of ways to improve a member's overall experience with the Fraternity. The information is used to ensure our site has relevant and user-friendly data, to deliver communications from Sigma Nu Fraternity, Inc. and Sigma Nu Educational, Inc. and from licensed service providers and licensed vendors, and to allow access to limited areas of our site, as appropriate.
Member Information
Our site stores (along with our main database) information we collect from you, cookies, log files, and/or third parties to create your member information. This information includes personally identifiable information and is used to create website content, correspondence, publications, and other goods and services to improve the overall membership value of the Fraternity experience. We also use this information to contact you, as outlined below.
Cookies
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is linked to personally identifiable information. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. For the session ID cookie, once a user closes the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user's hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. If a user rejects the cookies, he may still use our site
Log Files
Like most standard website servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, in some instances are tied to personally identifiable information to enable our Web-based service.
Clear GIFs
We employ a software technology called clear GIFs, that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear GIFs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear GIFs, in some instances, are tied to a user's personally identifiable information. Clear GIFs can "work with" existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same website.
Communications from Sigma Nu
We send all new users a welcoming e-mail to notify them when their account has been activated. There is no opting out option for this instance of communication.
The Delta Magazine and other correspondence
We use updated contact information to produce our mailing lists for The Delta magazine. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive this publication. Please see "Your Preferences" section. You may also opt to receive it electronically versus postal mail. From time to time, Sigma Nu Fraternity, Inc. and Sigma Nu Educational Foundation, Inc. will send correspondence, newsletters, solicitations, and general information through e-mail. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications via e-mail. Please see "Your Preferences" section. In addition, from time to time we will send correspondence, newsletters, solicitations, and general information by postal mail. If you wish to not receive such items, please contact the General Fraternity Headquarters.
Service Announcements
On rare occasions, it is necessary to send out a strictly service-related announcement. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send users an e-mail. Generally, users may not opt-out of these communications. However, these communications are not promotional or Fraternity related in nature.
Services
We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account. We reply via e-mail, postal mail, or phone.
Approved and Licensed Vendors
Sigma Nu actively screens and licenses the use of its trademarks to vendors that produce and sell goods and services which we feel will benefit members of the Fraternity. From time to time, these vendors will solicit their goods and services via e-mail and postal mail. Out of respect for the privacy of our users we present the option to not receive these types of communications via e-mail. Please see "Your Preferences" section.
Members Area Users
If the user has opted to allow some, or all, of his information to be viewed in the Membership Directory, this information can be viewed and used, subject to the Terms of Use, by other registered users of the website. This information is password-protected and can only be accessed by other users who have registered for the Members Area.
Sharing
Legal Disclaimer
Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information, when required by law, wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with, or respond to, current judicial proceedings, subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims, or if we believe that your actions violate applicable laws.
Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)
We share aggregated demographic information with certain business partners. This information is not linked to any personally identifiable information.
Third-party Intermediaries
From time to time, we use outside companies to ship orders, process credit card payments, and to mail certain items such as correspondence, solicitations, and The Delta magazine. These companies do not retain, share, store, or use personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes.
Service Providers and Licensed Vendors
We partner with other third-parties to provide specific goods and services. Sigma Nu actively screens and licenses the use of its trademarks to vendors that produce and sell goods and services which we feel will benefit members of Sigma Nu. We share aggregate, non-personally identifiable information, names, addresses, or e-mail addresses that are necessary for the third-party to provide notification of these goods and services. These third-parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the agreed upon purpose between them and the Fraternity.
Business Transactions
In the event that Sigma Nu Fraternity, Inc. or Sigma Nu Educational Foundation, Inc. goes through a business transaction, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. Users will be notified via a prominent notice on our website for 30 days or via an e-mail prior to a change of ownership, or control of, their personal information. If, as a result of the business transaction, the users' personally identifiable information will be used in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, they will be given choices consistent with our notification of changes section.
Security
Sigma Nu takes every precaution to protect our users' and members' information. When users submit sensitive information via the website, their information is protected both online and offline.
When any of our forms asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with Secured Socket Layered (SSL). All webpages are secured, as indicated by the lock icon in the address bar.
While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information offline. All of our users' information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted. All databases that store this information meet industry standard security specifications, and access is password protected. Only employees who need the information to perform specific job duties are granted access to personally identifiable information. Furthermore, all employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added; our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users' information is protected.
Correcting and Updating Your Information
If a user's information changes (such as zip code, phone, e-mail or postal address), or if a user no longer desires certain services, we provide a way to correct and update this information. This can usually be done in the Members Area or by contacting us by telephone, e-mail, or postal mail at the contact information listed below.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the home page, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact Sigma Nu Fraternity, Inc. or Sigma Nu Educational Foundation, Inc.:
Phone: (540) 463-1869Fax: (540) 463-1669Email: headquarters@sigmanu.orgMailing Address:9 North Lewis StreetP.O. Box 1869Lexington, VA 24450
About UsGeneral InformationCopyright NoticeTerms of UsePrivacy PolicyVision, Mission, and Strategic PlanThe Creed of Sigma Nu FraternityHistoryState of the Fraternity & FoundationVisiting HeadquartersFraternity LeadershipStaff DirectoryEmploymentMerchandiseOfficial Insignia & ArtworkInterfraternal InvolvementFifth Point Properties, LLCExpansionExpansion FAQExpansion ResourcesCurrent & Future ColoniesRecently Charted ChaptersIs Your Chapter Dormant?Chapter ListingActive Chapters & ColoniesDormant ChaptersMedia ReleasesCollegiate MembersPandemic PlanPast StatementsUpdated Pursuit of Excellence ProgramUpdated Chapter Consultation ProgramMental HealthBest Practices LibraryVirtual OperationsService and PhilathropyCampus LeadershipValues Congruent EnvironmentsIntellectual DevelopmentCandidate DevelopmentBrother DevelopmentAlumni DevelopmentRecruitment and ManpowerChapter OperationsGovernance and AccountabilityUsage and HistoryOfficer ResourcesCommanderLt. CommanderTreasurerRecorderRisk Reduction ChairmanScholarship ChairmanSocial ChairmanMarshalLEAD ChairmanHouse ManagerCommunity Service & Philanthropy ChairmanChaplainAlumni Relations ChairmanRecruitment ChairmanEducational ProgramsV-A-RAnti-Hazing InitiativeNational Hazing Prevention WeekHazingPrevention.OrgGreekLifeEduAlcoholEduBehind Happy FacesMental Health Quick TakesDignityUPoster SeriesStrengths WorkshopsGenerationRxDon't Play DoctorMentor NetworkAdvisorsAdviseesFAQScholarsHelping Hand InitiativePartnersMonth of ServiceCrowdChangeLEAD ProgramPhasesAll ChapterPhase IPhase IIPhase IIIPhase IVEvaluationFAQGet Started With LEADLeadership ResourcesSession EvaluationTeam BuildingLead ChairmanVolunteeringPursuit of ExcellenceIn-Person OperationsValues-Based LeadershipPersonal Development & Membership ValueOperational ExcellenceVirtual OperationsValues-Based LeadershipPersonal Development & Membership ValueOperational ExcellenceChapter Support ProgramValues-Based RecruitmentEducational MaterialsMarketing MaterialsMultimedia MaterialsRecruitment ResourcesChapter Consultation & SupportLeadership Consultation ProgramLeadership ConsultantsSchedulesBecome a ConsultantRisk ReductionChapter ResourcesWe Have A SituationRisk Reduction ChairmanSocial ChairmanSocial PlanningSpecial Event Request FormIncident Report FormEventsGrand ChapterCollege of ChaptersSigma Nu InstitutesCollegiate & Chapter AwardsLEAD Program AwardsPursuit of Excellence AwardsRock Chapter AwardsAlumni & VolunteersPandemic PlanHouse Corporation ResourcesAlumni Volunteer ResourcesMental HealthBecoming a VolunteerAlumni Advisory BoardsGuidelinesMentoring and AdvisingOfficer UpdateAssessment ProgramChapter AdvisorsRole of Chapter AdvisorsAlumni Best Practices LibraryAlumni Advisory BoardsHouse CorporationsAlumni DevelopmentAlumni EngagementUsage and HistoryMental Health ResourcesMentor NetworkAdvisorsAdviseesFAQHigh CouncilDivision CommandersRiley SocietyAlumni ChaptersPetitionGovernanceOperationsAnnual ReportListingSurveyAlumni ClubsGuidelinesListingRegister Your Alumni ClubEventsGrand ChapterSigma Nu Institutes150th Anniversary ReceptionsLocal EventsAlumni Awards & DistinctionsHall of HonorHall of Fame150th DirectoryChange of AddressProspective MembersGeneral InformationWhy Sigma NuLeadershipServiceAcademicsNo HazingLEAD ProgramValueHistoryThe FoundersHonorThe CreedVision and MissionProspective Member FormAre You a Legacy?Legacy Information for AlumniMembership ReferralActive Chapter & Colony ListingNotable Sigma Nu MembersScholarshipsInformation for ParentsLEADParticipantsPhase IPhase IIPhase IIIPhase IVEducational FoundationAbout the FoundationVision and MissionStrategic PlanBoard of DirectorsBrandon S. AversBen A. BuettellThomas J. BymarkCharles R. EitelTodd E. EliasonJohn A. HearnTimothy C. HuffmyerRobert J. LalanneDaniel W. MaslauskiJames R. MounierMaxwell L. SmithJonathan D. SprengerAlbert W. WursterStaffBrad BeachamDavid M. MainellaNicholas L. MurphyShannon T. BalserKenneth W. LewisVolunteer OpportunitiesCollegiate Board MemberYoung Alumnus Board MemberPrioritiesEmergency Scholarship FundInformation for Applicants150th Anniversary BrickSpears Family Epsilon Epsilon Center for ExcellenceDonation FormCollege of ChaptersNational Scholarship FundsFounders General Scholarship FundChapter Scholarship AccountsBeta Tau Chapter Scholarship AccountEpsilon Omicron Chapter Scholarship AccountEta Zeta Chapter Scholarship AccountTheta Kappa Chapter Scholarship AccountTheta Sigma Chapter Scholarship AccountKappa Lambda Chapter Scholarship AccountLambda Upsilon Chapter Scholarship AccountMu Zeta Chapter Scholarship AccountMichael Patrick Joyce (Mu Xi) Scholarship FundChapter Educational FundsBeta Zeta Chapter Educational FundBeta Theta Chapter Educational FundGamma Beta Chapter Educational FundLambda Epsilon Chapter Educational FundHeadquarters PropertyMemorial Flag Pavilion & War MemorialWays to GiveDonate NowUpdate Payment InformationAdvice 4 CommandersPlanned GivingThanks & Recognition1869 Club1869 Club Chapter Challenge1869 Club Donation PagePathway of HonorBrick Order FormMemorial Flag PavilionBrick Order FormWar MemorialDonor ListingCumulative GivingOmega SocietyYates Legacy SocietyEventsAtlanta Honorary BoardBlack & Gold SocietyWhy join the Black and Gold Society?What are the benefits and levels of the Black and Gold Society?How can I serve as a Black and Gold Society ambassador?Why do alumni support the Black and Gold Society?Black & Gold Society AmbassadorsAmbassador Sign-UpThe DeltaLatest NewsCurrent IssuePast IssuesBlog
ABOUT USGeneral InformationVision, Mission, and Strategic PlanThe Creed of Sigma Nu FraternityHistoryState of the Fraternity & FoundationVisiting HeadquartersFraternity LeadershipStaff DirectoryEmploymentMerchandiseInterfraternal InvolvementFifth Point Properties, LLCExpansionChapter ListingMedia Releases
COLLEGIATE MEMBERSBest Practices LibraryOfficer ResourcesEducational ProgramsMentor NetworkHelping Hand InitiativeLEAD ProgramValues-Based RecruitmentChapter Consultation & SupportRisk ReductionEventsCollegiate & Chapter Awards
ALUMNI & VOLUNTEERSBecoming a VolunteerAlumni Advisory BoardsChapter AdvisorsAlumni Best Practices LibraryMental Health ResourcesMentor NetworkHigh CouncilDivision CommandersRiley SocietyAlumni ChaptersAlumni ClubsEventsAlumni Awards & Distinctions150th DirectoryChange of Address
PROSPECTIVE MEMBERSGeneral InformationWhy Sigma Nu?HistoryProspective Member FormAre You A Legacy?Membership ReferralActive Chapter & Colony ListingNotable Sigma Nu MembersScholarshipsInformation for Parents
LEADParticipants
EDUCATIONAL
FOUNDATIONAbout the FoundationPrioritiesWays to GivePlanned GivingThanks & RecognitionEventsTHE DELTAIncident Report Form
LoveHonorTruth
© 2015-2020 Sigma Nu Fraternity, Inc.9 North Lewis Street, P.O. Box 1869, Lexington, Virginia 24450Phone: (540) 463-1869 | Fax: (540) 463-1669 | Email: headquarters@sigmanu.org
